<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: laptop $ | Ruby Xocolatl]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.juanger.com/blog/categories/laptop-/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.juanger.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-02T12:55:13-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.juanger.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Juan Castaneda]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADC Student Member]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.juanger.com/blog/2008/11/adc-student-member/"/>
    <updated>2008-11-10T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.juanger.com/blog/2008/11/adc-student-member</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I should have a new laptop now but awful things happen, specially in economy. Projects get cancelled and in contrast to the Mexican Peso a lot of things gain value, making me poorer and poorer(as I live in Mexico). But not everything is a bad new.

Last week, my ADC Orientation Kit arrived, I bought it three weeks ago at the Apple Online Store Mexico but the bad thing is that I haven't received any response to all my e-mails in which I ask for directions to use my hardware discount.

The good and cool things are:
<ul>
<li>I have a new Leopard copy and it is said that they will send me some more and any major update (Snow Leopard???)</li>
<li>The package is really like the one that was pictured at the online store (big and black). I expected only a brown box with things, but it's Apple...</li>
<li>I can apply for the WWDC scholarship program :)</li>
<li>I have a new t-shirt (black with the legend: icode). Again, it's Apple...</li>
<li>I <strike>supposedly</strike> have a discount at the Apple Online Store</li>
</ul>

The other thing that they send is the Monthly Developer DVD but it's not the big reason to get the membership, anything inside the DVD is downloadable from ADC site. 

Now the only remaining thing is to know how the Hardware Discount works in Mexico and peacefully wait for the Mexican Peso to gain some value...</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server Output in RoRGate]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.juanger.com/blog/2008/07/server-output-in-rorgate/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.juanger.com/blog/2008/07/server-output-in-rorgate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I've added a developer menu to the resulting apps in RoRGate, if you download the 0.3 beta version you will see the change:

<a onblur="try {parent.deselectBloggerImageGracefully();} catch(e) {}" href="http://github.com/juanger/rorgate/tree/master%2Fmeta%2Fimages%2FRoRGate-0.3b.png?raw=true"><img style="margin: 0px auto 10px; display: block; text-align: center; cursor: pointer; width: 400px;" src="http://github.com/juanger/rorgate/tree/master%2Fmeta%2Fimages%2FRoRGate-0.3b.png?raw=true" alt="" border="0" /></a>
With that, you as developer can use it to see your app in action, see the server output and edit it in TextMate.

The only thing is that the server output works strange with 2.x rails apps, I don't know why, but only the error output is displayed in such rails apps. I use the NSTask class with an NSPipe for both the standart output and error but with rails 2.x it behaves strangely.

<a onblur="try {parent.deselectBloggerImageGracefully();} catch(e) {}" href="http://github.com/juanger/rorgate/tree/master%2Fmeta%2Fimages%2FServerOut.png?raw=true"><img style="margin: 0px auto 10px; display: block; text-align: center; cursor: pointer; width: 400px;" src="http://github.com/juanger/rorgate/tree/master%2Fmeta%2Fimages%2FServerOut.png?raw=true" alt="" border="0" /></a>
Also I've embedded RubyCococa, but I can't make it work in both Leopard and Tiger because of libffi.dylib. Leopard's RubyCocoa has it installed in /usr/lib and I don't know where it is in Tiger. Maybe the solution is to create a Tiger version and a Leopard version, but I'm very lazy and I'd rather have only one.

Lastly, I need a new laptop (many of my friends will agree) and because of that, I've added a donations pledgie badge for RoRGate and some ads here in my blog. I'm a student and I own an iBook G3 which has been giving me a lot of trouble lately, so as I'm most of the time at school (school's computers ain't good either) deploying to or developing for a lot of platforms I need a new one, one in which running a single unit test doesn't seem to last forever and I hope some of you(friends or not) could help me. My-new-laptop blogthon :) has begun.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
